mobilesmspk.net 2012-12-30

# Privacy Policy - MobileSMSPK.net

## Privacy Policy

> Privacy Policy as stated below governs your use of MobileSMSPK.net site. By using this site, you agree to and approve of our Privacy Policy as set out below. 
> 
> All terms not defined in this document have the meanings ascribed to them in the Terms of Use Agreement between you and MobileSMSPK.net which by use of this Site you agree to accept. 
> 
> MobileSMSPK.net (legal owner and the operator of this site) considers and respects an individual's privacy very seriously. 
> 
> The fundamental purpose of the services that MobileSMSPK.net provides requires that we gather, process, use and distribute the member's information which you provide directly by filling out our various forms and formats; for example, gender, city and country of residence, occupation, interests, etc. Therefore, MobileSMSPK.net does not guarantee that your information will be protected from exposure in any particular party or group. In fact the purpose of this web site is to connects people through their personal networks and allows them to meet others. If you wish to remove your profile, please Contact Us. 
> 
> ### 1\. The Information We Collect
>
>> At the time you register to become a Registered User of the Site, you will be asked to fill out a registration form which requires you provide information such as your name, email address, date of birth and other personal information. 
>> 
>> We also collect personal information submitted by our users in filling out their profile such city and country of residence, occupation, interests, qualifications, etc. We collect this personal information when our users:  
> 
>> 
>>   1. Sign up as a member.
>>   2. Make changes to their member profile information.
>>   3. Members at MobileSMSPK.net may choose to provide additional information beyond their basic profile. Providing additional information beyond what is required at registration is entirely optional, but enables our users to better identify each other and more effectively connect and interact with each other.
>> 

>> 
>> MobileSMSPK.net also collects information from users that is unique, but cannot be linked to a specific individual, such as IP address and browser type. A user's session will be tracked, but each user will remain anonymous. We gather this information on all visitors to www.MobileSMSPK.net for systems administration purposes and to track user trends, such as our popular mobile phones feature. 
> 
> ### 2\. Disclosure of Information
>
>> We will not sell, lease or exchange your profile information to third parties without first obtaining your express consent, unless required by law or to protect your membership. 

> ### 3\. Cookies
>
>> We use "cookies" to store specific information about you and track your visits to our Site. It is not uncommon for web sites to use cookies to enhance identification of their users. 
>> 
>> A "cookie" is a small amount of data that is sent to your browser and stored on your computer's hard drive. A cookie can be sent to your computer's hard drive only if you access our Site using the computer. 
>> 
>> If you do not de-activate or erase the cookie, each time you use the same computer to access our Site, our web servers will be notified of your visit to our Site and in turn we have knowledge of your visit and the pattern of your usage. 
>> 
>> Cookies help us understand how members use MobileSMSPK.net, which allows us to improve upon the service. Members who disable cookies may not be able to use certain features of MobileSMSPK.net. 
> 
> ### 4\. Links to Other Websites
>
>> The MobileSMSPK.net site may contain links to other Web sites. Please be aware that MobileSMSPK.net is not responsible for the privacy practices of other sites our users choose to visit. If our users provide any information directly to parties other than MobileSMSPK.net, different rules may apply to the use or disclosure of the personal information disclosed. We encourage you to investigate and ask questions before disclosing your personal information to third parties. 
> 
> ### 5\. User Surveys
>
>> From time to time, MobileSMSPK.net may contact registered members to ask that they participate in user surveys. Participation in these surveys is purely voluntary, and any personally identifiable information submitted will not be shared with people who are not employees of MobileSMSPK.net. 
> 
> ### 6\. Changes to Privacy Policy
>
>> Any changes to this Privacy Policy will be communicated through our posting an amended and restated Privacy Policy on our Site. 
>> 
>> Our posting the amended and restated Privacy Policy will make such new Privacy Policy immediately effective. 
>> 
>> You agree that all Collected Information (whether or not collected prior to or after the new policy became effective) will be governed by the newest Privacy Policy then in effect. 
> 
> ### 7\. Contacting Us
>
>> If you have any questions about this Privacy Policy, the practices of this site, or your dealings with this Web site, you can contact at: **admin@mobilesmspk.net**
> 
> (Last Updated on September 1, 2012)
